<odoo>
    <record id="mail_template_sale_order" model="mail.template">
        <field name="name">SO Mail Template</field>
        <field name="model_id" ref="sale.model_sale_order"/>
<!--        <field name="email_from">"{{ object.user_id.name }}" &lt;{{ (object.user_id.email_formatted) }}&gt;-->
<!--        </field>-->
        <field name="email_to">{{ object.acknowledgement_email_list }}</field>
        <field name="subject">Acknowledgement of Sample Receipt – Report No {{ object.name }} </field>
        <field name="body_html" type="html">
            <div style="font-family: Arial, sans-serif; line-height: 1.5; color: #333;">
                <p>Dear <strong><t t-out="object.partner_id.name"/></strong>,
                </p>
                <p>Thank you for giving us the opportunity to test your products.</p>
                <p>We acknowledge the receipt of your sample. Please find below the details along with the expected test
                    report delivery timeline:
                </p>

                <hr style="border: 1px solid #e0e0e0; margin: 20px 0;"/>

                <div style="margin-bottom: 15px;">
                    <p>
                        <strong>Manufacturer:</strong>
                        <t t-out="object.partner_id.name"/>
                        <br/>
                        <strong>Applicant:</strong>
                        <t t-out="object.tti_pi_applicant.name or N/A"/>
                        <br/>
                        <strong>Buyer:</strong>
                        <t t-out="object.tti_pi_buyer.name or N/A"/>
                        <br/>
                        <strong>Report No.:</strong>
                        <t t-out="object.name or N/A"/>
                        <br/>
                        <strong>Sample Receiving Date/Time:</strong>
                        <t t-out="object.create_date.strftime('%d/%m/%y') or N/A"/>
                        <br/>
                        <strong>Expected Report Delivery:</strong>
                        <t t-out="object.commitment_date.strftime('%d/%m/%y') or N/A"/>
                    </p>
                </div>

                <hr style="border: 1px solid #e0e0e0; margin: 20px 0;"/>

                <h3 style="color: #2E69A6; margin-bottom: 10px;">Invoice &amp; Payment:</h3>
                <p>Please find the attached sale order. To ensure timely delivery of the test report, we request you to
                    arrange payment at your earliest convenience.
                </p>
                <p>Any discrepancy in the sale order must be reported <strong>on the same working day</strong> of
                    receipt of this email. Otherwise, the sale order and invoice will be deemed correct, testing will
                    proceed accordingly, and your organization will be liable for the invoiced amount.
                </p>
                <p>Also attached is a copy of our <strong>Terms &amp; Conditions</strong> for your reference.
                </p>

                <hr style="border: 1px solid #e0e0e0; margin: 20px 0;"/>

                <h3 style="color: #2E69A6; margin-bottom: 10px;">Withholding Tax (WHT) Compliance:</h3>
                <p>Please share the relevant <strong>Withholding Tax Certificates / CPRs</strong> at:
                </p>
                <p>📧
                    <strong>Creditcontrol2@ttilabs.net</strong>
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>As per Section 153(1)(b):</strong>
                    <br/>
                    <em>"Where tax is collected/deducted by a person other than the Federal/Provincial Government, it
                        must be deposited in the Government Treasury or a designated bank within 7 days from the end of
                        the week (ending every Sunday)."
                    </em>
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>Note:</strong>
                    CPRs must be submitted within <strong>30 days</strong> of deduction. Failure to do so will result in
                    the amount being adjusted against your next invoice.
                </p>

                <hr style="border: 1px solid #e0e0e0; margin: 20px 0;"/>

                <p>
                    <strong>Disclaimer:</strong>
                    <br/>
                    Final testing charges on the Invoice may vary from this sale order based on actual testing
                    performed, any changes in the test requisition, or addition/removal of tests.
                </p>

                <hr style="border: 1px solid #e0e0e0; margin: 20px 0;"/>

                <p>Thank you for choosing <strong>Textile Testing International</strong>.
                </p>

                <p>Best regards,
                    <br/>
                    <strong>Customer Services</strong>
                    <br/>
                    Textile Testing International
                    <br/>
                    ISO 17025 Accredited Lab
                    <br/>
                    347-S, Quaid-e-Azam Industrial Estate
                    <br/>
                    Kot Lakhpat, Lahore -- 54500, Pakistan
                    <br/>
                    Tel: (92-42) 111-786-001 | Fax: (92-42) 3515-4555
                    <br/>
                    📧 customerservices@ttilabs.net | 🌐
                    <a href="https://ttilabs.net/" style="color: #2E69A6;">www.ttilabs.net</a>
                </p>

                <hr style="border: 1px solid #e0e0e0; margin: 20px 0;"/>

                <p style="font-size: 0.9em; color: #666;">
                    <em>Note: This is a system-generated message and does not require a signature.</em>
                </p>
            </div>

            <hr style="border: 1px solid #e0e0e0; margin: 20px 0;"/>

            <div style="font-size: 0.9em; color: #555;">
                <h3 style="color: #2E69A6; margin-bottom: 15px;">TERMS AND CONDITIONS FOR TESTING</h3>

                <ol style="padding-left: 20px; margin-bottom: 20px;">
                    <li style="margin-bottom: 10px;">Textile Testing International will conduct tests in accordance with
                        and subject to the terms and the conditions herein contained. The conditions may only be
                        modified
                        by a variation expressed in writing and signed on behalf of the company by a Director and no
                        other action on the part of Textile Testing International or its employees or agents shall be
                        construed as an acceptance of any other terms and conditions.
                    </li>

                    <li style="margin-bottom: 10px;">It shall be the responsibility of the client to ascertain and
                        notify Textile Testing International of the standards with which any sample submitted for
                        testing must comply in any country or territory in which the sample concerned is intended to be
                        sold. In default of specific instructions Textile Testing International will adopt the test
                        methods and standards considered most appropriate. When the test method proposed by the customer
                        is considered to be inappropriate or out of date, the customer is communicated accordingly for
                        approval.
                    </li>

                    <li style="margin-bottom: 10px;">The client will ensure that clear instructions are provided to
                        Textile Testing International in due time to enable the required services to be performed
                        effectively. Any deviation required by the customer shall not affect the validity of results and
                        acceptable to customer and Tit.
                    </li>

                    <li style="margin-bottom: 10px;">In case of any deviation from the contract, Tti will inform the
                        customer through proper mean.
                    </li>

                    <li style="margin-bottom: 10px;">Textile Testing International with subject to the clients
                        requirements test any sample submitted to it or sampled by Textile Testing
                        International from bulk to ascertain its conformity or otherwise with contract description or
                        sample. In no circumstances wil t Textile
                        Testing International render any opinion as to the fitness of any sample from the purpose for
                        which it is said to be intended unless in
                        any specific case Textile Testing International is requested so to do and agrees so to do in
                        writing.
                    </li>

                    <li style="margin-bottom: 10px;">A Test Report issued by Textile Testing International shall refer
                        only to the sample actually tested and shall not refer or be deemed to
                        refer to bulk from which such a sample may be said to have been obtained.
                    </li>

                    <li style="margin-bottom: 10px;">Tti will ensure confidentiality of information obtained in the
                        laboratory ac tivities and the proprietary rights of clients are protected. Test
                        reports issued by Textile Testing International are subject to the condition that they are not
                        to be made public or used in c onnection
                        with or for the purpose of any advertising promotional or publicity undertaking or material
                        whatsoever without the express consent in
                        writing of hereto first obtained.
                    </li>

                    <li style="margin-bottom: 10px;">In situations where Tti is required by law or competent authority
                        to release confidential information, the client is notified , unless
                        prohibited by law, of the information provided.
                    </li>

                    <li style="margin-bottom: 10px;">In the event that any Test Report issued by the Textile Testing
                        International is required for use in connection with or for e vidence in
                        any Court or Arbitration proceedings, Tti Testing Laboratories will render all assistance and
                        explanation reasonably required in
                        connection wherewith all costs and expenses incurred by Textile Testing International in giving
                        such assistance or explanatio ns shall
                        be borne by the client to whose order the Test Report in question was prepared.
                    </li>

                    <li style="margin-bottom: 10px;">Tti observes confidentiality of information about the client
                        obtained indirectly, such as complainant or regulators and the i nformation
                        provider (source) identity shall also be kept confidential unless agreed.
                    </li>

                    <li style="margin-bottom: 10px;">In no circumstance will the issuing of any Test Report by Textile
                        Testing International operate or be deemed or purport to involve
                        Textile Testing International as a party or agent in any other way in any relationship
                        contractual or otherwise between the c lient for
                        whom the Test Report shall have been prepared and any other party whom so ever.
                    </li>

                    <li style="margin-bottom: 10px;">In the event that any test report shall be proven inaccurate and
                        that inaccuracy thereof shall have been caused by the act or default of
                        Textile Testing International or its technicians or agents then and in any such case the
                        liability of Textile Testing International shall be
                        limited to retesting or refunding to client of whom the Test Report shalt have made free of
                        interest the fee paid to Textile Testing
                        International.
                    </li>

                    <li style="margin-bottom: 10px;">In the process of testing Textile Testing International may use any
                        alternate method or input which had been tested through internal
                        testing to have the same effect. Due to unavailability or unavoidable circumstances.
                    </li>

                    <li style="margin-bottom: 10px;">Samples received at Textile Testing International without
                        sufficient information to proceed with testing and samples for which the
                        client does not give a clear consent to bear the cost of the required or requested testing, will
                        be held and stored for a max imum of 30
                        days after which they would be disposed.
                    </li>

                    <li style="margin-bottom: 10px;">The Textile Testing International shall be entitled at its
                        discretion to delegate the performance of the whole or any part of the services
                        contracted for with the principal to any agent or subcontractor.
                    </li>

                    <li style="margin-bottom: 10px;">Every Officer, employee, agent or subcontractor of Textile Testing
                        International shall have the benefit of the limitation of liability and
                        the indemnities contained in the general conditions. So far as relates to such limitation and
                        indemnities, any contract enter ed into by
                        the Textile Testing International is entered into not only its own behalf but also as agent and
                        trusty for every such person as
                        aforesaid.
                    </li>

                    <li style="margin-bottom: 10px;">If the requirements of the client necessitate the analysis of
                        sample by the principal or by any 3rd party, Textile Testing In ternational
                        will pass on the result of the analysis but without responsibility for its accuracy. Where the
                        Textile Testing International is on ly able to
                        witness an analysis by the principal or be any 3rd party the Textile Testing International will
                        provide confirmation, if such be the case
                        that a correct sample has been analysed but will not otherwise be responsible for the accuracy
                        of such analysis.
                    </li>

                    <li style="margin-bottom: 10px;">Tti reserves the right to file a suite in the court of law to
                        recover the due amount in the case of non -payment in 65 days.
                    </li>

                    <li style="margin-bottom: 10px;">Samples for testing will be disposed off at the discretion of
                        Textile Testing International after expiry of 30 days or mentio ned
                        otherwise, from the date of test report, unless a written request and pick up arrangements are
                        made by client for their return.
                    </li>

                    <li style="margin-bottom: 10px;">Payment Terms: Test charges need to be paid in advance.
                    </li>

                    <li style="margin-bottom: 10px;">On the request of Client, Textile Testing International may forward
                        Samples/Test Reports to the Clients or to the buyer or agent of the Client and all costs
                        involved in such a request to be borne by the Client.
                    </li>

                    <li style="margin-bottom: 10px;">This report shall not be reproduced except in full without prior
                        authorization from Textile Testing International.
                    </li>

                    <li style="margin-bottom: 10px;">Statement of conformity and measurement uncertainty will only be
                        provided where required and agreed by the client. On the basis of provided specification,
                        standard with the application of clearly defined decision rule.
                    </li>
                </ol>

                <p style="margin-bottom: 5px;">347-S, Quaid-e-Azam Industrial Estate, Kot Lakhpat, Lahore- 54770
                    Pakistan.
                </p>
                <p style="margin-bottom: 5px;">UAN: +92 42 111786001 | URL:
                    <a href="https://ttilabs.net/" style="color: #2E69A6;">www.ttilabs.net</a>
                </p>

                <hr style="border-top: 1px dashed #ccc; margin: 15px 0;"/>

                <p style="font-size: 0.8em; color: #777; text-align: center;">
                    <strong>ISO/IEC 17025 Accredited Lab | ICPSC Accredited Lab | ISO/IEC 17020 Accredited Inspection
                        Agency | EPA Certified Lab
                    </strong>
                </p>
            </div>
        </field>
    </record>
</odoo>